> > Jem Young: 现在我们来谈谈贝壳。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So
now we'll talk about shells.
什么是 shell?
What is a shell?
我给你个提示
I'll give you a hint.
你刚刚用了五秒钟
You just used one five seconds ago.
嗯。
Yes.
>> 扬声器 2: Bash。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Bash.
>> Jem Young: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah.
>> 扬声器 2: 缺省情况下包含在许多 Unix 系统中的扬声器，但是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Is the one that's included
with a lot of Unix systems by default, but
它基本上允许您运行命令行。
it basically allows you
to run command lines.
和 Unix一起运行很多基本的系统。
And run a lot of the basic systems
that that come along with Unix.
>> Jem Young: 正确的答案。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Exactly right, good answer.
Shell 只是用于与系统接口的命令解释器。
The shell is just a command interpreter
to interface with a system.
就像我说的 80 年代的 80 年代我正在和我自己约会
Like I said, in the old days, the 80s,
[LAUGH] I'm dating myself now.
这不是很久以前你所拥有的
Not that long ago, that's all you had.
当你坐在电脑上的时候你就把这个眨眨了
You just had this blinking cursor
when you sat down on a computer and
真的是恐吓和人，我做什么 ?
is really intimidating and
people are, what do I do?
不容易找到可以运行的命令。
There's no easy way to figure
out which commands you can run.
Heck，你可能都不知道你刚坐的是哪个操作系统
Heck, you probably didn't even know which
operating system you're on if you just sat
在一个随机的计算机上
down on a random computer.
但贝壳只是跟操作系统说话的一种方式
But shells are just a way
of talking to the OS,
与其他与系统交谈的应用程序交谈。
to talk to the other applications
talking to the system.
终端是我们在这里的应用。
The terminal is the application
that we're in here.
所以我正在运行 iTerm ，它很受欢迎。
So I'm running iTerm which
it's pretty popular.
有些人可能有点不同
Some of you are probably
running something different.
如果您正在使用 Windows ，那么可能正在使用 PowerShell 或类似的内容。
If you're using Windows, you're probably
using PowerShell or something like that.
但终端只是外壳上的包装器
But Terminal it's just a wrapper
on shell applications.
一些较为流行的应用是 Bash，
And some of the more popular
shell applications are Bash,
这才是我们今天用的
that's what we're using today.
也许我们会再检查一次
Probably, we'll check in a second.
扎克是个很受欢迎的人
ZSH is a really popular one.
还有，我不去所有这些，因为它们不相关。
There's more, I won't go into all of
them because they're not relevant.
但 Bash 是你最常看到的最主要的
But Bash is the primary one that
you're probably gonna see most often.
而且在你需要的每个操作系统上。
And it's on every operating
system that you need.
>> Jem Young: 而且，就像我之前说的，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And, like I've said before,
外壳就是那个最前线的界面
the shell is just that
frontline that's the interface.
它是一个用户界面，它只是与一个应用程序或操作系统进行对话。
It is a user interface of sorts, and
it just talks to an application or the OS,
是与内核的对话
which talks to the kernel.
内核是操作系统的核心。
And the kernel is the core
of the operating system.
这就是做所有工作的事情，它与实际机器层对话。
That's the thing that does all the work,
it talks to the actual machine layer.
所以使用这个外壳的伟大之处在于我们没有远离
So the great thing about using the shell
is we're not that far removed from
在下面运行的实际代码
the actual code that's running underneath.
Versus 是一个 GUI ，它是除去的几个步骤。
Versus a GUI which is
a few more steps removed.
因为这通常会在某种形式上与外壳交谈
Because that's usually gonna talk
to the shell in some sort or
以这种方式运行命令。
run commands in that way.
如果要显示您所使用的 shell ，那么可以输入， echo $0。
If you wanna show the shell that
you're in, you can type, echo $0.
所以，让我们现在来尝试，回声，它会重复我的意思。
So let's try that now, echo,
which echo just repeats what I'm saying.
我要它说 $ 0， $ 只是一个扩展，它扩展了 0 变量。
I want it to say $0, $ is just an
expansion and that expands the 0 variable.
它说我们在巴什
And it says we're in bash.
如果你不在巴什你应该告诉我
If you're not in Bash,
you should let me know.
你可能是在巴什人除非有人告诉你要下载些什么
You're probably in Bash though, unless
someone told you to download something,
你应该用 SH
you should use the SH.
这就更酷了
It's way cooler, which,
我也不会再讨论今天的辩论了
again, I'm not gonna get into that
debate today about which one is better.
但我们会用巴什的标准
But we'll use Bash because
it's standardized.